1. Sign in
Role-based access for submitters, approvers, and admins.
2. Dashboard
Backlog health, action queue, and activity feed for operators.
3. Submit request
Capture business intent, priority, and target application.
4. Request triage
Search, filter, and sort the enhancement backlog.
5. Request detail
AI analysis, mission control metrics, and impact recommendations.
6. React collaboration
SignalR live comments and presence on the React SPA.
7. System Map
Code and database artifacts linked in a knowledge graph.
8. Cytoscape graph
Interactive zoom, pan, and type-colored nodes.
9. Schema drift
Compare live database schema against code mappings.
10. Approval queue
Human approve, reject, or clarify before export.
11. React approvals
Mobile-friendly queue with keyboard navigation.
12. Onboarding wizard
Register app, connect code, database, and run discovery.
13. Applications
Team-scoped portfolio with repos and intelligence.
14. Database connections
Read-only schema registration for drift and ERD.
15. Background jobs
Hangfire indexing, discovery, and AI analysis queues.
16. Tenancy & billing
Plans, Stripe checkout, and schema-per-tenant isolation.
17. Compliance
SOC 2 readiness, retention, and audit export.
18. End-to-end flow
Intake → grounded AI → human approval → ticket export.