Sign in
Role-based access for submitters, approvers, and admins. SSO via Entra ID supported.
Dashboard control room
Backlog health at a glance: pending analysis, high-risk approvals, sparklines, and the action queue for your role.
Submit enhancement request
Capture business intent, priority, and target application — the foundation for grounded AI impact analysis.
Request triage
Search, filter, and sort the enhancement backlog. Risk badges highlight what needs attention first.
Request detail & AI analysis
Mission control shows risk, confidence, affected apps/repos, and DB recommendations from your indexed estate.
React detail + real-time collaboration
SignalR powers live comments, viewer presence, and analysis refresh on the React SPA hot path.
System Map
Graph links controllers, entities, services, and tables — architects see blast radius before approving.
Interactive Cytoscape graph
Zoom, pan, and select nodes by type. Graph/list toggle with a 400-node performance cap.
Schema drift detection
Scheduled scans compare live database schema against code mappings to catch mismatches early.
Approval queue
Human gate: approve, reject, or request clarification. Audit log records every decision.
React approval queue
Mobile-friendly queue with J/K keyboard navigation and quick decision actions.
Onboarding wizard
Register apps via local path, ZIP, GitHub App, or Git — then connect DB and run discovery.
Application portfolio
Team-scoped applications with linked repositories, DB connections, and intelligence profiles.
Database connections
Register read-only connections for schema scan, ERD export, and drift detection.
Background jobs
Hangfire orchestrates indexing, discovery, and AI analysis with retry and admin visibility.
Tenancy & billing
Multi-tenant plans, Stripe checkout, trial enforcement, and schema-per-tenant isolation.
Compliance & governance
SOC 2 readiness, retention policies, audit export, and security whitepaper for procurement.
Intake → analysis → approval → export
EnhancementHub deploys in your environment. Business request to Jira-ready ticket — with full audit trail.